{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "category": "History",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Which%20one%20of%20these%20was%20not%20a%20beach%20landing%20site%20in%20the%20Invasion%20of%20Normandy%3F",
            "correct_answer": "Silver",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Gold",
                "Juno",
                "Sword"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "History",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In%20what%20year%20did%20the%20Wall%20Street%20Crash%20take%20place%3F",
            "correct_answer": "1929",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "1932",
                "1930",
                "1925"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "History",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "The%20Spitfire%20originated%20from%20a%20racing%20plane.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "History",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Which%20modern%20day%20country%20is%20the%20region%20that%20was%20known%20as%20Phrygia%20in%20ancient%20times%3F",
            "correct_answer": "Turkey",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Syria",
                "Greece",
                "Egypt"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "History",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In%201720%2C%20England%20was%20in%20massive%20debt%20and%20became%20involved%20in%20the%20South%20Sea%20Bubble.%20Who%20was%20the%20main%20mastermind%20behind%20it%3F",
            "correct_answer": "John%20Blunt",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Daniel%20Defoe",
                "Robert%20Harley",
                "John%20Churchill"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "History",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In%20World%20War%20ll%2C%20Great%20Britian%20used%20inflatable%20tanks%20on%20the%20ports%20of%20Great%20Britain%20to%20divert%20Hitler%20away%20from%20Normandy%2FD-day%20landing.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "History",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Adolf%20Hitler%20was%20tried%20at%20the%20Nuremberg%20trials.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "History",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "To%20what%20political%20party%20did%20Abraham%20Lincoln%20belong%20when%20elected%20POTUS%3F",
            "correct_answer": "Republican",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Democrat",
                "Independent",
                "Whig"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "History",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Which%20modern%20country%20is%20known%20as%20%22The%20Graveyard%20of%20Empires%22%3F",
            "correct_answer": "Afghanistan",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "China",
                "Iraq",
                "Russia"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "History",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In%20what%20year%20did%20the%20Great%20Northern%20War%2C%20between%20Russia%20and%20Sweden%2C%20end%3F",
            "correct_answer": "1721",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "1726",
                "1727",
                "1724"
            ]
        }
    ]
}